{
    "subject": "resource/Josiah_Duane_Hicks",
    "predicate": "property/state",
    "object": "resource/Pennsylvania",
    "human_readable": "Josiah Duane Hicks was from Pennsylvania.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9078153967857361,
            "question": "Where was Josiah Duane Hicks from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5910660028457642,
            "question": "Who were some influential people from Josiah Duane Hicks' time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48506850004196167,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Josiah Duane Hicks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4155345857143402,
            "question": "Is there anything notable about Josiah Duane Hicks' life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40449026226997375,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Josiah Duane Hicks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4016692340373993,
            "question": "What impact did Josiah Duane Hicks have on his community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3317857086658478,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19954614341259003,
            "question": "What state is Pennsylvania known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1470695286989212,
            "question": "What is the history of Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09322744607925415,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Pennsylvania?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Josiah Duane Hicks was from Pennsylvania.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3955_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Pennsylvania?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3955_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Pennsylvania known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3955_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from Pennsylvania?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3955_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3955_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Josiah Duane Hicks was from Pennsylvania.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention his service in the U.S. House of Representatives from Pennsylvania and provide details about his residence in Altoona, PA."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}